Eugenics Record Office Records 1670-1964 Mss.Ms.Coll.77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Trait Files, 1670-1964 (Box Series I: 1-65)
  - A:18 - A:1976 (Box Series I-29)
    - Ichthyosis, 1758-1929; A:1965 (Box Series I-29)
      - Toney, Alligator Skin Boy, Dreamland Circus Side Show, Coney Island, N. Y., 1927; A:1965-1 (Box Series I-29)
      - Susi: "The Elephant Skin Girl", 1929; A:1965-2 (Box Series I-29)
    - Adenoma Sebaceum, 1918-1926; A:1967 (Box Series I-29)
    - Skin Tumors, 1899; A:19671 (Box Series I-29)
    - Naevus Flammens, 1918; A:1968 (Box Series I-29)
    - Keloids, n.d.; A:1969 (Box Series I-29)
    - Birthmark, 1924-1927; A:197 (Box Series I-29)
    - Telangiectasia, 1876-1924; A:1975 #1 (Box Series I-29)
    - Telangiectasia, 1924-1927; A:1975 #2 (Box Series I-29)
    - Hemorrhagic Telangiectasia, 1921-1934; A:19751 (Box Series I-29)
    - Naevus Verrucosus, 1925; A:1976 (Box Series I-29)
  - A:198 - A:209 #2 (Box Series I-30)
    - Moles, 1919-1927; A:198 (Box Series I-30)
    - Other Diseases of the Skin, 1924-1929; A:199 (Box Series I-30)
    - Thickening of Bones, 1918, 1925; A:20 (Box Series I-30)
    - Large Boned, 1919; A:201 (Box Series I-30)
    - Craniofacial Dysostosis, 1912-1929; A:2042 (Box Series I-30)
    - Brittle Bones, 1897-1926; A:206 #1 (Box Series I-30)
    - Brittle Bones, 1833-1926; A:206 #2 (Box Series I-30)
    - Brittle Bones, 1915-1925; A:206 #3 (Box Series I-30)
    - Ankylosis, 1898-1925; A:207 (Box Series I-30)
    - Radio-Ulnar Synovitis, 1872-1925; A:2072 #1 (Box Series I-30)
    - Radio-Ulnar Synovitis, 1924-1925; A:2072 #2 (Box Series I-30)
    - Congenital Radial Displacement, 1926; A:2074 (Box Series I-30)
    - Rhizomelic Spondylosis, 1920; A:2075 (Box Series I-30)
    - Congenital Contractures, 1905-1931; A:2078 (Box Series I-30)
    - Osteosclerosis, 1922-1934; A:208 (Box Series I-30)
    - Osteititis Deformans (Paget's Disease), 1905-1930; A:2082 (Box Series I-30)
    - Achondroplasia, 1902-1934; A:2081 #1 (Box Series I-30)
    - Achondroplasia, 1911-1915; A:2081 #2 (Box Series I-30)
    - Achondroplasia [ contains Davenport correspondence], 1906-1931; A:2081 #3 (Box Series I-30)
    - Exostoses, 1866-1921; A:209 #1 (Box Series I-30)
    - Exostoses, 1822-1933; A:209 #2 (Box Series I-30)
  - A:209 #3 - A:212 (Box Series I-31)
    - Exostoses, 1856-1923; A:209 #3 (Box Series I-31)
    - Exostoses, 1849-1935; A:209 #4 (Box Series I-31)
    - Appendicular Skeleton, 1902-1925; A:21 (Box Series I-31)
    - General Form of Hand and Foot, 1906-1935; A:210 (Box Series I-31)
    - General Form of Hand and Foot, 1916; A:201a (Box Series I-31)
    - Malformations of Extremities, 1922-1935; A:2101 (Box Series I-31)
    - Deformed Hands, 1913-1932; A:2104 (Box Series I-31)
    - Club Hand, 1912-1928; A:21044 (Box Series I-31)
    - Deformed Foot, 1913-1935; A:2105 (Box Series I-31)
    - Club Foot, 1909-1926; A:21054 (Box Series I-31)
    - Turning in Foot, 1924, 1934; A:21055 (Box Series I-31)
    - Hammer-Toe, 1912, 1934; A:21056 (Box Series I-31)
    - Bunions, 1919; A:21057 (Box Series I-31)
    - Overlapping Toes, 1932, 1934; A:21058 (Box Series I-31)
    - Polydactylism, 1864-1921; A:2106 #1 (Box Series I-31)
      - Foot exhibiting polydactylism, n.d.; A:2106 (Box Series I-31)
    - Polydactylism, 1915-1930; A:2106 #2 (Box Series I-31)
    - Polydactylism, 1915-1930; A:2106 #3 (Box Series I-31)
    - Heptadactylism, 1915; A:21062 (Box Series I-31)
    - Syndactylism, 1896-1928; A:211 #1 (Box Series I-31)
    - Syndactylism [ contains photos], 1919-1932; A:211 #2 (Box Series I-31)
    - Cleft Hands, 1912-1919; A:2111 (Box Series I-31)
    - Absence of Digits [ contains photos], 1909-1935; A:212 (Box Series I-31)
  - A:2121 - A:21906 (Box Series I-32)
    - Absence of Bones, 1897-1929; A:2121 (Box Series I-32)
    - Extra Bones, 1900, 1932; A:21212 (Box Series I-32)
    - Ainhum, 1884-1921; A:2124 (Box Series I-32)
    - Absence of Hands or Feet [ contains photos], 1916-1930; A:2125 (Box Series I-32)
    - Finger Joints, 1921, 1928; A:213 (Box Series I-32)
    - Double Jointed Fingers, 1911-1932; A:2131 (Box Series I-32)
    - Brachydactylism, 1838-1936; A:214 (Box Series I-32)
    - Clubbed Fingers, 1919, 1924; A:2141 (Box Series I-32)
    - Flat Thumbs, 1929-1930; A:21412 (Box Series I-32)
    - Short Fingers, 1902-1933; A:2143 #1 (Box Series I-32)
    - Short Fingers [ contains photos], 1932-1934; A:2143 #2 (Box Series I-32)
    - Undeveloped Fingers, 1915; A:2144 (Box Series I-32)
    - Hypophalangism, 1923-1924; A:2145 (Box Series I-32)
    - Length of Digits, 1914-1934; A:215 (Box Series I-32)
    - Shape of Fingers, 1920, 1927; A:2151 (Box Series I-32)
    - Slender Fingers, 1919; A:2152 (Box Series I-32)
    - Crooked Fingers, 1913-1933; A:216 (Box Series I-32)
    - Crooked Little Finger, 1915; A:216a (Box Series I-32)
    - Dupuytren's Contracture, 1912-1934; A:2165 (Box Series I-32)
    - Sinisterity, 1911-1934; A:217 #1 (Box Series I-32)
    - Sinisterity, 1913-1929; A:217 #2 (Box Series I-32)
    - Sinisterity, 1925-1936; A:217 #3 (Box Series I-32)
    - Righthandedness, 1928; A:2175 (Box Series I-32)
    - Ambidexterity, 1923, 1929; A:218 (Box Series I-32)
    - Limbs--Short - Abnormal, 1922; A:219 (Box Series I-32)
    - Short Limbs, 1913-1920; A:21902 (Box Series I-32)
    - Long Limbs, 1924; A:21904 (Box Series I-32)
    - Synovitis of Long Bones, 1922; A:21905 (Box Series I-32)
    - Luxation of Long Bones [ contains photos], 1912-1932; A:21906 (Box Series I-32)
  - A:2191 - A:25211 (Box Series I-33)
    - Cripple, 1911, 1914; A:2191 (Box Series I-33)
    - Luxation of Hip, 1880-1933; A:21911 (Box Series I-33)
    - Hip Joint Disease, 1925; A:21912 (Box Series I-33)
    - Supernumerary Limbs [ contains pictures], 1927, 1929; A:2192 (Box Series I-33)
    - Absence or Defects of Arms or Legs [ contains photos], 1921-1934; A:2193 (Box Series I-33)
    - Knee, 1893-1930; A:21931 (Box Series I-33)
    - Bow Legs, 1923; A:2195 (Box Series I-33)
    - Knock Knee, 1933; A:2196 (Box Series I-33)
    - Trophoneurosis of Limbs, 1924; A:2197 (Box Series I-33)
    - Cranial, 1868-1923; A:22 (Box Series I-33)
    - Facial Asymmetry, 1919-1920; A:2202 (Box Series I-33)
    - Parietal Bones, 1895-1926; A:2206 (Box Series I-33)
    - Defects in Facial and Cranial Development, 1923-1932; A:2207 (Box Series I-33)
    - Cyclopia, 1916, 1921; A:22072 (Box Series I-33)
    - Hydrocephaly, 1897-1933; A:221 (Box Series I-33)
    - Microcephaly, 1920-1929; A:222 (Box Series I-33)
    - Oxycephaly, 1931, 1934; A:2222 (Box Series I-33)
    - Brachycephaly, n.d.; A:223 (Box Series I-33)
    - Skull, 1922, 1929; A:224 (Box Series I-33)
    - Dolichocephaly, 1907-1913; A:225 (Box Series I-33)
    - Short - Low - Round - Face, 1923; A:226 (Box Series I-33)
    - Peculiar Forehead, 1924; A:228 (Box Series I-33)
    - High Forehead, 1919-1933; A:2281 (Box Series I-33)
    - Low Forehead (American Indians), 1908; A:2286 (Box Series I-33)
    - Jaw Bone, 1923; A:229 (Box Series I-33)
    - Prognathism, 1924; A:2297 (Box Series I-33)
    - Pointed Chin, 1919; A:2298 (Box Series I-33)
    - Vertebral Skeleton, 1904; A:23 (Box Series I-33)
    - Spina Bifida, 1922-1935; A:231 (Box Series I-33)
    - Scoliosis, 1831-1934; A:232 (Box Series I-33)
    - Torticollis, 1912-1921; A:2325 (Box Series I-33)
    - Kyphosis, 1909-1924; A:233 (Box Series I-33)
    - Lordosis, n.d.; A:234 (Box Series I-33)
    - Longicoccyx, 1901, 1924; A:235 (Box Series I-33)
    - Rib Variations, 1922, 1924; A:236 (Box Series I-33)
    - Neck Length, 1933; A:237 (Box Series I-33)
    - Defects of Spine, 1912, 1920; A:239 (Box Series I-33)
    - Clavicles, 1875-1934; A:243 (Box Series I-33)
    - Scapula, 1910-1926; A:244 (Box Series I-33)
    - Funnel Breasted, 1922; A:2451 (Box Series I-33)
    - Pelvic Girdle, 1934; A:246 (Box Series I-33)
    - Myopathy, 1913-1930; A:251 (Box Series I-33)
    - Muscular Atrophy [ contains photos], 1873-1934; A:252 (Box Series I-33)
    - Atrophy of Hands, 1908-1909; A:25211 (Box Series I-33)
  - A:2524 - A:312 (Box Series I-34)
    - Charcot - Marie - Tooth Type, 1925; A:2524 (Box Series I-34)
    - Progressive Bulbar Paralysis, 1922, 1932; A:2525 (Box Series I-34)
    - Ligaments, 1925; A:253 (Box Series I-34)
    - Ossification of Ligaments, n.d.; A:2532 (Box Series I-34)
    - Thomsen's Disease, 1875-1933; A:254 (Box Series I-34)
    - Myotonia Atrophica, 1911-1925; A:2541 (Box Series I-34)
    - Paramyotonia, 1916; A:2542 (Box Series I-34)
    - Joint Hypotonia, 1916-1928; A:2543 (Box Series I-34)
    - Myositis Ossificans Progressiva, 1912; A:2546 (Box Series I-34)
    - Ataxia, 1906-1933; A:255 (Box Series I-34)
    - Trembling, 1887-1931; A:256 (Box Series I-34)
    - Chvostek's Sign, 1914; A:2572 (Box Series I-34)
    - Other Diseases of the Muscles, 1929; A:258 (Box Series I-34)
    - Hernia of Diaphragm, 1922; A:258731 (Box Series I-34)
    - Other Defects of the Muscles, 1930; A:259 (Box Series I-34)
    - Shortening of Muscles, 1902, 1926; A:2591 (Box Series I-34)
    - Dimples, General, 1933; A:2595 (Box Series I-34)
    - Defects of Special Muscles, 1923; A:2597 (Box Series I-34)
    - Hernia, 1895-1930; A:264 (Box Series I-34)
    - Inguinal Hernia, 1910-1927; A:2642 (Box Series I-34)
    - Umbilical Hernia, n.d.; A:2644 (Box Series I-34)
    - Facial, 1921-1922; A:27 (Box Series I-34)
    - Frown, 1924; A:272 (Box Series I-34)
    - Dimple - Chin - Cheek, 1913-1933; A:275 (Box Series I-34)
    - Nose, 1919-1928; A:28 (Box Series I-34)
    - Internal Growths of Nose, 1925; A:280 (Box Series I-34)
    - Long Nose, 1920-1933; A:283 (Box Series I-34)
    - Prominent Nose - Roman, 1913-1926; A:284 (Box Series I-34)
    - Pug Nose, 1919-1933; A:285 (Box Series I-34)
    - Nose, Protuberance, 1914; A:286 (Box Series I-34)
    - Bump on Nose, n.d.; A:2861 (Box Series I-34)
    - Other Diseases of the Nose, 1934; A:288 (Box Series I-34)
    - Ecdysis of Lining of Membrane of Nose, 1912; A:2891 (Box Series I-34)
    - External Ear, 1919, 1923; A:29 (Box Series I-34)
    - Fistula of Ear, 1911; A:29014 (Box Series I-34)
    - Ear - Lobule, 1923; A:293 (Box Series I-34)
    - Absence of Lobule of Ear, 1924; A:2933 (Box Series I-34)
    - Double Lobed Ear, 1933; A:2935 (Box Series I-34)
    - Protruding Ears, 1918, 1929; A:2951 (Box Series I-34)
    - Large Ears, n.d.; A:2952 (Box Series I-34)
    - Nervous System, 1910-1928; A:3 (Box Series I-34)
    - Nervous System (General), 1897-1926; A:30 (Box Series I-34)
    - Convulsions, 1913, 1920; A:301 (Box Series I-34)
    - Neuritis, 1923; A:302 (Box Series I-34)
    - Nervous Reflexes, 1924; A:305 (Box Series I-34)
    - Sympathetic Nerves, 1924; A:306 (Box Series I-34)
    - Spinal Chord and Brain, 1935; A:31 #1 (Box Series I-34)
    - Spinal Chord and Brain, 1905-1926; A:31 #2 (Box Series I-34)
    - Anencephal, 1917; A:312 (Box Series I-34)
  - A:3121 - A:3134 #3 (Box Series I-35)
    - Aplasia Axialis Extracorticalis, 1910; A:3121 (Box Series I-35)
    - Constitutional Inferiority, 1930, 1934; A:313 (Box Series I-35)
    - Mental Defectives, 1916, 1919; A:313 (Box Series I-35)
    - Idiocy, 1917-1926; A:3131 (Box Series I-35)
    - Imbecility, 1918; A:3132 (Box Series I-35)
    - Amaurotic Family Idiocy, 1909-1925; A:31321 #1 (Box Series I-35)
    - Amaurotic Family Idiocy, 1898-1930; A:31321 #2 (Box Series I-35)
    - Amaurotic Family Idiocy, 1905-1926; A:31321 #3 (Box Series I-35)
    - Mongolian Idiocy [ contains photos], 1906-1930; A:31322 #1 (Box Series I-35)
    - Mongolian Idiocy [ contains photos], 1927, 1936; A:31322 #2 (Box Series I-35)
    - Feeblemindedness, 1898-1918; A:3134 #1 (Box Series I-35)
    - Feeblemindedness, 1909-1920; A:3134 #2 (Box Series I-35)
    - Feeblemindedness, 1903-1927; A:3134 #3 (Box Series I-35)
      - "Exhibit of Work and Educational Campaign for Juvenile Mental Defectives", ca. 1915; A:3134-17 (Box Series I-35)
      - Burden of the feebleminded, A:3134-22 (Box Series I-35)
  - A:3134 #4 - A:316 #1 (Box Series I-36)
    - Feeblemindedness, 1909-1932; A:3134 #4 (Box Series I-36)
      - Pedigree for feeblemindedness, A:3134-44 (Box Series I-36)
    - Feeblemindedness, 1920-1928; A:3134 #5 (Box Series I-36)
    - Feeblemindedness, 1926; A:3134 #6 (Box Series I-36)
    - Blank Forms Used for Admission, Record, Diagnosis, Etc., 1910, n.d.; A:3134 #7 (Box Series I-36)
    - Moral Incapability, 1921; A:3135 (Box Series I-36)
    - Degeneracy, 1888-1928; A:31352 (Box Series I-36)
    - Pauperism, 1909-1937; A:3138 (Box Series I-36)
    - Epilepsy, 1911-1917; A:314 #1 (Box Series I-36)
      - Report of the Commission to Investigate the Question of the Increase of Criminals, Mental Defectives, Epileptics and Degenerates, 1911; A:314-8 (Box Series I-36)
    - Epilepsy, 1907-1934; A:314 #2 (Box Series I-36)
    - Epilepsy, 1901-1934; A:314 #3 (Box Series I-36)
    - Psychic Epilepsy, 1910-1924; A:3144 (Box Series I-36)
    - Myoclonia, 1921, 1924; A:3145 (Box Series I-36)
    - Insanity, 1908-1930; A:316 #1 (Box Series I-36)
  - A:316 #2 - A:3161 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1905-1933; A:316 #2 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1896-1925; A:316 #3 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1916-1917; A:316 #4 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1919; A:316 #5 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1919-1920; A:316 #6 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1920; A:316 #7 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1921-1923; A:316 #8 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1923; A:316 #9 (Box Series I-37)
    - Insanity, 1921-1922; A:316 #10 (Box Series I-37)
    - Arteriosclerotic Insanity, 1913; A:3161 (Box Series I-37)
  - A:3162 #1 - A:318 (Box Series I-38)
    - Dementia Praecox, 1920-1938; A:3162 #1 (Box Series I-38)
    - Dementia Praecox, 1924; A:3162 #2 (Box Series I-38)
    - Dementia Praecox--Hebephrenic, 1920; A:31621 (Box Series I-38)
    - Catatonia, 1923; A:31622 (Box Series I-38)
    - Manic Depressive Insanity, 1911-1935; A:3164 #1 (Box Series I-38)
    - Manic Depressive Insanity, 1909-1923; A:3164 #2 (Box Series I-38)
    - Mania, n.d.; A:31641 (Box Series I-38)
    - Involutional Melancholia, 1915-1925; A:31646 (Box Series I-38)
    - Paranoia, 1915-1925; A:3165 (Box Series I-38)
    - Senile Dementia, 1926; A:3166 (Box Series I-38)
    - Presenile Dementia, 1933; A:31661 (Box Series I-38)
    - Paresis; Dementia Paralytica, 1896-1921; A:3167 (Box Series I-38)
    - Delirium Tremens, 1912; A:3168 (Box Series I-38)
    - Constitutional Psychopathic State, 1896-1934; A:317 (Box Series I-38)
    - Psychasthenia, 1933; A:3170 (Box Series I-38)
    - Nymphomania, 1916; A:3172 (Box Series I-38)
    - Sex Offense, 1913; A:3174 #1 (Box Series I-38)
    - Sex Offense, 1910-1930; A:3174 #2 (Box Series I-38)
    - Eroticism, 1930; A:31744 (Box Series I-38)
    - Sex Perversion, 1925; A:3176 (Box Series I-38)
    - Sex Inversion, 1934; A:3177 (Box Series I-38)
    - Neuropathic Constitution, 1912-1934; A:318 (Box Series I-38)
  - A:3181 #1 - A:31812 S #3 (Box Series I-39)
    - Chorea, 1908-1919; A:3131 #1 (Box Series I-39)
    - Chorea, 1913-1931; A:3181 #2 (Box Series I-39)
    - Chorea, 1915-1933; A:3181 #3 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1892-1949; A:31812 #1 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1909-1932; A:31812 #2 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1911-1912; A:31812 #3 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1905-1914; A:31812 #4 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, n.d.; A:31812 #5 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1911; A:31812 S #1 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1911; A:31812 S #2 (Box Series I-39)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1905-1911; A:31812 S #3 (Box Series I-39)
  - A:31812 S #4 - Dight Institute #7 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1905-1911; A:31812 S #4 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea, 1910-1911; A:31812 S #5 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Correspondence, 1951-1953; Dight Institute #1 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Index of Names, 1964; Dight Institute #2 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #3 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #4 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #5 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #6 (Box Series I-40)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #7 (Box Series I-40)
  - Dight Institute #8 - A:31883 (Box Series I-41)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #8 (Box Series I-41)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Patient Records, [194-]; Dight Institute #9 (Box Series I-41)
    - Huntington's Chorea--Pedigree Charts, n.d.; Dight Institute #10 (Box Series I-41)
    - Neurasthenia, 1909; A:3182 (Box Series I-41)
    - Hysteria, n.d.; A:3183 (Box Series I-41)
    - Quick Temper, 1907-1935; A:31833 (Box Series I-41)
    - Catalepsy, 1923; A:31835 (Box Series I-41)
    - Enuresis, 1912-1924; A:31837 (Box Series I-41)
    - Somnambulism, 1919-1936; A:318383 (Box Series I-41)
    - Somniloquism, 1925; A:318384 (Box Series I-41)
    - Gritting Teeth in Sleep, 1920; A:318385 (Box Series I-41)
    - Migraine, 1931; A:3184 #1 (Box Series I-41)
    - Migraine, 1915-1916; A:3184 #2 (Box Series I-41)
    - Migraine, 1915; A:3184 #3 (Box Series I-41)
    - Migraine, 1897-1934; A:3184 #4 (Box Series I-41)
    - Migraine, 1913-1935; A:3184 #5 (Box Series I-41)
    - Headache, 1919, 1935; A:31842 (Box Series I-41)
    - Wanderlust, 1908-1934; A:3185 (Box Series I-41)
    - Wanderer, 1927; A:31857 (Box Series I-41)
    - Vertigo, 1935; A:3188 (Box Series I-41)
    - Fainting Easily, 1924; A:31883 (Box Series I-41)
  - A:319 - A:336 (Box Series I-42)
    - Speech Defect, 1889-1928; A:319 (Box Series I-42)
    - Stammering, 1914-1932; A:3191 (Box Series I-42)
    - Stuttering, 1919-1933; A:3192 (Box Series I-42)
    - Lisping, 1928; A:3194 (Box Series I-42)
    - Tongue Tied, 1920; A:3199 (Box Series I-42)
    - Cerebrum, n.d.; A:32 (Box Series I-42)
    - Brain Trouble, 1920; A:320 (Box Series I-42)
    - Apoplexy, 1919-1924; A:321 (Box Series I-42)
    - Cerebellar Ataxia, 1919-1934; A:32315 (Box Series I-42)
    - Sclerosis of the Brain, 1925-1934; A:3233 (Box Series I-42)
    - Encephalitis, 1923-1927; A:324 (Box Series I-42)
    - Meningitis, 1924, 1932; A:325 (Box Series I-42)
    - Locomotor Ataxia, 1914-1935; A:326 (Box Series I-42)
    - Cerebellar Atrophy, 1926; A:327 (Box Series I-42)
    - Cerebrum, Degeneration of, 1924, 1926; A:3281 (Box Series I-42)
    - Sclerosis, 1876-1933; A:331 #1 (Box Series I-42)
    - Sclerosis, 1897-1923; A:331 #2 (Box Series I-42)
    - Multiple Sclerosis, 1921; A:331 #3 (Box Series I-42)
    - Speeches, n.d.; ----- (Box Series I-42)
    - Ataxia, Friedrich's, 1887-1932; A:3311 #1 (Box Series I-42)
    - Ataxia, Friedrich's, 1884-1917; A:3311 #2 (Box Series I-42)
    - Ataxia, Friedrich's, 1879-1927; A:3311 #3 (Box Series I-42)
    - Myoseism, 1892-1922; A:3312 (Box Series I-42)
    - Poliomyelitis, 1910-1934; A:3323 (Box Series I-42)
    - Congenital Palsy, 1891-1920; A:333 (Box Series I-42)
    - Spastic Spinal Paralyis, 1889-1933; A:3331 (Box Series I-42)
    - Paralysis Agitans, 1912-1925; A:335 (Box Series I-42)
    - Progressive Paralysis, 1873-1934; A:336 (Box Series I-42)
  - A:3361 - A:3418 #2 (Box Series I-43)
    - Progressive Muscular Atrophy, 1884, 1914; A:3361 (Box Series I-43)
    - Muscular Atrophy, 1899-1931; A:3362 (Box Series I-43)
    - Pseudo-Hypertrophic Muscular Atrophy, 1934; A:3367 (Box Series I-43)
    - Muscular Dystrophy, 1891; A:3368 (Box Series I-43)
    - Muscular Atrophies - Facio, Scapulo, Humeral Form, 1912, 1921; A:33691 (Box Series I-43)
    - Nervous Swelling and Nervous Tumors, 1926; A:337 (Box Series I-43)
    - Angioneurotic Oedema, 1905-1929; A:33711 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1918-1934; A:33712 #1 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1874-1918; A:33712 #2 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1870-1920; A:33712 #3 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1824-1915; A:33712 #4 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1818-1922; A:33712 #5 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1818-1905; A:33712 #6 (Box Series I-43)
    - Von Recklinghausen's Disease, 1906-1925; A:33712 #7 (Box Series I-43)
    - Neurotic Condition, 1913, 1922; A:338 (Box Series I-43)
    - Syringomyelia, 1930; A:3381 (Box Series I-43)
    - Paralysis, 1898-1935; A:341 (Box Series I-43)
    - Cerebral Palsies, 1913; A:34101 (Box Series I-43)
    - Hemiplegia, n.d.; A:3414 (Box Series I-43)
    - Facial Paralysis, 1912, 1920; A:3415 (Box Series I-43)
    - Paraplegia, 1895-1913; A:3416 (Box Series I-43)
    - Spastic Paraplegia, 1909-1930; A:34163 (Box Series I-43)
    - Facial Palsy, n.d.; A:34171 (Box Series I-43)
    - Paralysis of Extremities, 1920; A:34172 (Box Series I-43)
    - Paralysis of Throat, 1915; A:341763 (Box Series I-43)
    - Periodic Paralysis, 1887-1934; A:3418 #1 (Box Series I-43)
    - Periodic Paralysis, 1882-1926; A:3418 #2 (Box Series I-43)
  - A:34182 - A:3523 (Box Series I-44)
    - Periodic Paralysis Due to Cold, 1886-1916; A:34182 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, n.d.; A:35 #1 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, 1909, 1911; A:35 #2 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, 1909-1911; A:35 #3 (Box Series I-44)
      - "Hereditary Criminality and its Certain Cure", 1909; A:35-9 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, 1907-1934; A:35 #4 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, 1924; A:35 #5 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, n.d.; A:35 #6 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, n.d.; A:35 #7 (Box Series I-44)
    - Criminality, 1911, 1914; A:35 #8 (Box Series I-44)
    - Polygamy, 1910-1922; A:3512 (Box Series I-44)
    - Incest, 1924, 1926; A:3515 (Box Series I-44)
    - Prostitution, 1910-1911; A:3516 (Box Series I-44)
    - Drunkenness, 1925; A:3523 (Box Series I-44)
  - A:3532 - A:423261 (Box Series I-45)
    - Homicide, 1918; A:3532 (Box Series I-45)
    - Suicide, 1908-1933; A:3535 (Box Series I-45)
    - Abortion, 1918-1922; A:3537 (Box Series I-45)
    - Mendicancy, A:35442 (Box Series I-45)
    - Larceny, 1922; A:3546 (Box Series I-45)
    - Nervous Diseases, 1925, 1929; A:38 (Box Series I-45)
    - Mental Traits, 1890-1928; A:4 (Box Series I-45)
    - Special Mental Traits, 1914; A:40 (Box Series I-45)
    - Special Resurgent Impressions and Ideas, 1925; A:406 (Box Series I-45)
    - Nightmares, 1920; A:40621 (Box Series I-45)
    - Hallucinations, Auditory, 1916; A:40642 (Box Series I-45)
    - Intellectual Faculties, 1921, 1932; A:41 (Box Series I-45)
    - Mental Ability, 1904-1933; A:410 (Box Series I-45)
    - Mental Precocity, 1915-1924; A:4101 #1 (Box Series I-45)
    - Mental Precocity, 1920-1934; A:4101 #2 (Box Series I-45)
    - Mental Tests, 1930; A:4108 (Box Series I-45)
    - Visionary, 1926; A:4147 (Box Series I-45)
    - Memory, 1910-1929; A:415 (Box Series I-45)
    - Visual Memory, 1924; A:41511 (Box Series I-45)
    - Memory, Selective, 1925; A:4156 (Box Series I-45)
    - Association, 1917; A:4161 (Box Series I-45)
    - Tone Deafness, 1924-1933; A:41972 (Box Series I-45)
    - Color Hearing (Farbenhören), 1923; A:4198 (Box Series I-45)
    - General Tastes, 1920; A:421 (Box Series I-45)
    - Artistic Temperament, 1913; A:4211 (Box Series I-45)
    - Sense of Rhyme, 1919; A:42112 (Box Series I-45)
    - Sense of Humor, 1920-1932; A:4215 (Box Series I-45)
    - Love of Study, 1920-1925; A:4231 (Box Series I-45)
    - Love of Religion, 1925-1934; A:42312 (Box Series I-45)
    - Love of Animals, 1919-1930; A:423159 (Box Series I-45)
    - Love of Horses, 1928; A:4231595 (Box Series I-45)
    - Study of Medicine, 1930-1934; A:423161 (Box Series I-45)